Lesson 8 is quality management.
So these are the learning objectives for
quality.
First of all, we want to define quality.
Exactly what is quality.
There are different definitions of
quality, but for the purpose of the PMP
exam, there's one definition that you need
to know, so we'll talk about that.
We'll also talk about how it differs from
another term called grade.
So what's the difference between grade and
quality?
We'll be discussing that.
You also need to understand or recognize
the cost of quality, right?
So quality or the cost,
like to either build quality in
or the cost of failures is a
direct cost to your project.
So we'll be talking about that, all the
different categories of cost of quality.
And then plus, what's the highest level of
cost when it comes to quality?
What are the increasing levels of quality
costs?
So we'll discuss that as well plus the
basic agile approach to quality management
right and plus other different approaches
to quality management so we'll be talking
about some of the tools and techniques and
of course you also need to understand and
recognize what are some of the artifacts
right some of the documents right
regarding quality right and for both
quality control and quality assurance so
we'll also be defining then with the
difference and between quality control and
quality assurance and then some of the
tools that are required and some of the
artifacts and the documents that we're
going to be creating.